{
  "swedish": [
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Jobba",
      "rightAnswer": "arbeta",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hoppa", "leka", "springa"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Löpa",
      "rightAnswer": "springa",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hoppa", "leka", "arbeta"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Skutta",
      "rightAnswer": "hoppa",
      "wrongAnswer": ["springa", "leka", "arbeta"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Skriva",
      "rightAnswer": "notera",
      "wrongAnswer": ["läsa", "måla", "rita"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Läsa",
      "rightAnswer": "studera",
      "wrongAnswer": ["skriva", "leka", "hoppa"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Rita",
      "rightAnswer": "teckna",
      "wrongAnswer": ["måla", "klippa", "klistra"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Måla",
      "rightAnswer": "färglägga",
      "wrongAnswer": ["rita", "klippa", "skriva"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Klippa",
      "rightAnswer": "skära",
      "wrongAnswer": ["klistra", "måla", "läsa"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Klistra",
      "rightAnswer": "limma",
      "wrongAnswer": ["klippa", "rita", "skriva"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Bygga",
      "rightAnswer": "konstruera",
      "wrongAnswer": ["riva", "klippa", "leka"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Simma",
      "rightAnswer": "bada",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hoppa", "springa", "leka"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Spela",
      "rightAnswer": "leka",
      "wrongAnswer": ["arbeta", "skriva", "hoppa"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Sova",
      "rightAnswer": "vila",
      "wrongAnswer": ["vakna", "springa", "leka"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Vakna",
      "rightAnswer": "stiga upp",
      "wrongAnswer": ["sova", "äta", "springa"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Äta",
      "rightAnswer": "förtära",
      "wrongAnswer": ["dricka", "sova", "leka"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Dricka",
      "rightAnswer": "klunka",
      "wrongAnswer": ["äta", "sova", "hoppa"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Leka",
      "rightAnswer": "bus",
      "wrongAnswer": ["jobba", "hoppa", "skriva"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Gunga",
      "rightAnswer": "svänga",
      "wrongAnswer": ["springa", "leka", "skutta"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Dans",
      "rightAnswer": "dansa",
      "wrongAnswer": ["sjunga", "hoppa", "leka"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Sjunga",
      "rightAnswer": "tralla",
      "wrongAnswer": ["dansa", "hoppa", "spela"],
      "category": "verb"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Boll",
      "rightAnswer": "kula",
      "wrongAnswer": ["docka", "bil", "bok"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Docka",
      "rightAnswer": "leksak",
      "wrongAnswer": ["boll", "bil", "bok"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Bil",
      "rightAnswer": "fordon",
      "wrongAnswer": ["boll", "docka", "bok"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Bok",
      "rightAnswer": "roman",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bil", "boll", "docka"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Stol",
      "rightAnswer": "säte",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bord", "säng", "soffa"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Bord",
      "rightAnswer": "yta",
      "wrongAnswer": ["stol", "säng", "soffa"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Säng",
      "rightAnswer": "bädd",
      "wrongAnswer": ["stol", "bord", "soffa"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Soffa",
      "rightAnswer": "divan",
      "wrongAnswer": ["stol", "bord", "säng"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Skola",
      "rightAnswer": "läroanstalt",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hem", "parken", "affär"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Hem",
      "rightAnswer": "bostad",
      "wrongAnswer": ["skola", "parken", "affär"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Park",
      "rightAnswer": "grönområde",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hem", "skola", "affär"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Affär",
      "rightAnswer": "butik",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hem", "skola", "parken"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Hund",
      "rightAnswer": "vovve",
      "wrongAnswer": ["katt", "häst", "fågel"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Katt",
      "rightAnswer": "misse",
      "wrongAnswer": ["hund", "häst", "fågel"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Häst",
      "rightAnswer": "springare",
      "wrongAnswer": ["katt", "hund", "fågel"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Fågel",
      "rightAnswer": "pippi",
      "wrongAnswer": ["katt", "häst", "hund"],
      "category": "noun"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Röd",
      "rightAnswer": "skär",
      "wrongAnswer": ["blå", "gul", "grön"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Blå",
      "rightAnswer": "azur",
      "wrongAnswer": ["röd", "gul", "grön"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Gul",
      "rightAnswer": "kanariegul",
      "wrongAnswer": ["röd", "blå", "grön"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Grön",
      "rightAnswer": "lime",
      "wrongAnswer": ["röd", "blå", "gul"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Stor",
      "rightAnswer": "jättelik",
      "wrongAnswer": ["liten", "smal", "tunn"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Liten",
      "rightAnswer": "pytteliten",
      "wrongAnswer": ["stor", "bred", "hög"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Snabb",
      "rightAnswer": "kvick",
      "wrongAnswer": ["långsam", "trög", "seg"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Långsam",
      "rightAnswer": "saktfärdig",
      "wrongAnswer": ["snabb", "kvick", "alert"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Glad",
      "rightAnswer": "lycklig",
      "wrongAnswer": ["ledsen", "arg", "trött"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Ledsen",
      "rightAnswer": "sorgsen",
      "wrongAnswer": ["glad", "lycklig", "trött"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Arg",
      "rightAnswer": "förbannad",
      "wrongAnswer": ["glad", "lycklig", "trött"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Trött",
      "rightAnswer": "utmattad",
      "wrongAnswer": ["pigg", "glad", "arg"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Pigg",
      "rightAnswer": "alert",
      "wrongAnswer": ["trött", "glad", "arg"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Stark",
      "rightAnswer": "kraftig",
      "wrongAnswer": ["svag", "skör", "liten"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Svag",
      "rightAnswer": "skör",
      "wrongAnswer": ["stark", "kraftig", "stor"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Bred",
      "rightAnswer": "vid",
      "wrongAnswer": ["smal", "tunn", "hög"],
      "category": "adjective"
    },
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "Smal",
      "rightAnswer": "tunn",
      "wrongAnswer": ["bred", "vid", "stor"],
      "category": "adjective"
    }
  ]
}

